hometime.com 2010-05-11

# HOMETIME Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY

Our Commitment To Privacy 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

The Information We Collect 

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Hometime Video Publishing, Inc. website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

**Name  
Address   
Email address   
Phone number   
Credit/Debit Card Information **

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: 

**Name  
Address   
Phone Number **

The Way We Use Information 

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

You can register with our on-line store which may, in the future, enable you to receive Hometime newsletters and information about special offers. Information you submit on our on-line store will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

Third-Party Advertisers

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Our Commitment To Data Security 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

Our Commitment To Children's Privacy 

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information 

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting Hometime Customer Service at 800-489-9955 Ext.132 or at [Feeedback@Hometime.com](mailto:Feedback@Hometime.com). We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

How To Contact Us 

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 800-489-9955 Ext.132 or send us an email at [Feedback@Hometime.com](mailto:Feedback@Hometime.com).
